export const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is primary memory?",
    options: [
      "An internal component which holds data and programs that are not currently in use",
      "An external component which holds data and programs that are currently in use",
      "An internal component which holds data and programs that are currently in use",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the two types of primary memory?",
    options: ["RAM and ROM", "Flash memory and cache memory", "Flash memory and virtual memory"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "In terms of memory, what does volatile mean?",
    options: [
      "The memory retains its contents when the power is removed",
      "The memory can be overwritten",
      "The memory loses its contents when the power is removed",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these statements about ROM is true?",
    options: [
      "ROM is non-volatile and can only be read from",
      "ROM is volatile and can only be read from",
      "ROM is non-volatile and can be read from and written to",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these statements about RAM is true?",
    options: [
      "RAM is non-volatile and can only be read from",
      "RAM is volatile and can only be read from",
      "RAM is volatile and can be read from and written to",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is virtual memory?",
    options: ["High-speed internal memory", "Secondary storage used as additional RAM", "High-speed external memory"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is cache memory used for?",
    options: ["Temporarily holding frequently used data and instructions", "Extending the available RAM", "Extending the available ROM"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of secondary storage?",
    options: ["To hold data and programs that are currently in use", "To store data and programs long-term", "To extend RAM"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which type of computers usually have no need for secondary storage?",
    options: ["General purpose computers", "Tablet computers", "Embedded computers"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What type of storage is a hard disk drive?",
    options: ["Optical", "Magnetic", "Flash"],
    answer: 1,
  },
];
